Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum B
Yale University Divinity School Library
- United Board Consolidated General File, Series II
  - Gaume, Matilda, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 314)
  - Geier, Paul E., 1965-1979 (Box 23, Folder 315)
  - General Commission on Chaplains and Armed Forces Personnel, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 315)
  - General Service Foundation, 1965-1978 (Box 23, Folder 316)
  - Geng, George and Chow Mu-ling, 1965-1976 (Box 23, Folder 317)
  - Genting Highlands College, Malaysia, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 318)
  - Gentry, W. Max, 1958-1979 (Box 23, Folder 319)
  - George, Mary Belle, 1971-1979 (Box 23, Folder 320)
  - Georgi, Edith, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 321)
  - Germany, Charles H., 1965-1974 (Box 23, Folder 322)
  - Germany - Protestant Central Agency for Developmental Aid, 1972-1977 (Box 23, Folder 323)
  - Germino, Dante, 1969-1975 (Box 23, Folder 324)
  - Getaz, James L., 1969-1979 (Box 23, Folder 325)
  - Gibson, Henrietta, 1962-1964 (Box 23, Folder 325)
  - Giezentanner, M., 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 325)
  - Giffin, Alice, 1973-1979 (Box 23, Folder 326)
  - Gillespie, Mabel L., 1961-1967 (Box 23, Folder 326)
  - Ginling Alumnae Association, 1975,1977 (Box 23, Folder 327)
  - Ginling Alumnae Welfare Fund, 1957-1974 (Box 23, Folder 328)
  - Ginling Association in America, 1971-1977 (Box 23, Folder 329)
  - Ginling Girls' Middle School, Taiwan, 1966-1979 (Box 24, Folder 330)
  - Ginling College - Reeves Scholarships, 1955-1961 (Box 24, Folder 331)
  - Ginling College - Smith College: historical relationship, 1945-1968 (Box 24, Folder 332)
  - Gleason Charitable Fund, 1965-1969 (Box 24, Folder 333)
  - Gleysteen, Mrs. William, 1960-1975 (Box 24, Folder 333)
  - Glidden, Winifred B., 1968-1979 (Box 24, Folder 334)
  - Global Education Associates, 1973-1979 (Box 24, Folder 335-336)
  - Godard, James M., 1964-1970 (Box 24, Folder 337)
  - Goheen, Robert F., 1971-1978 (Box 24, Folder 337)
  - Gomez, Hilario / Muslim-Christian Dialogue Program, Philippines, 1972-1980 (Box 24, Folder 338)
  - Goo, Tin Chong, 1971-1977 (Box 24, Folder 339)
  - Goodrich, L. Carrington, 1966-1979 (Box 24, Folder 340)
  - Goodson, Judith, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 341)
  - Goodwin, Charles, 1966-1979 (Box 24, Folder 342)
  - Goolsby, George S., 1964-1978 (Box 24, Folder 343)
  - Gordon, Edith - Estate of, 1971-1976 (Box 24, Folder 343)
  - Goshen College, 1971-1979 (Box 24, Folder 344)
  - Goucher, John F. - Trust Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 345)
  - Gowing, Peter G., 1969-1979 (Box 25, Folder 346)
  - Grace Foundation, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 347)
  - Grace, Paul M., 1968 (Box 25, Folder 347)
  - Graham, Thomas W., 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 348)
  - Granner, Justine E., 1970-1978 (Box 25, Folder 348)
  - Graves, Alfred J., 1961-1979 (Box 25, Folder 349)
  - Graves, Linda, 1959-1964 (Box 25, Folder 350)
  - Graves, Stella Marie, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 351)
  - Gray, Albert L., 1960-1974 (Box 25, Folder 351)
  - Gray, Patrick J., 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 352)
  - Gray, Wallace, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 352)
  - Green, A. Margaret, 1961-1970 (Box 25, Folder 353)
  - Green, Diana, 1971-1978 (Box 25, Folder 353)
  - Greenberg, Harry, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 354)
  - Greenmont-Oak Park Community Church, OH, 1965-1974 (Box 25, Folder 354)
  - Greer, Charles, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - Gregorian, Phebe, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 356)
  - Gregorio, Samuel, 1968-1979 (Box 25, Folder 357)
  - Grey, Anna B., 1966-1978 (Box 25, Folder 358)
  - Grinnell-in-China, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 358)
  - Grose, Robert F., 1963-1979 (Box 25, Folder 359)
  - Gross, John O., 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 360)
  - Guerrant, Barnett and Mary, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 360)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 361)
  - Guhse, Edwin J., 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 361)
  - Guidelines for academic programs and medical education programs (UBCHEA documents), 1974 (Box 25, Folder 362)
  - Gunnison Community Church, CO, 1961-1967 (Box 25, Folder 362)
  - Gurnee Community Church, IL, 1962-1973 (Box 25, Folder 363)
  - Haa - Hoz (Box 26, Folder 364-371)
  - Hs - Hz (Box 27, Folder 372-373)
  - Hagdon, Mary C. - Estate of, 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 374)
  - Hagedorn Fund, 1964-1973 (Box 27, Folder 374)
  - Hales Charitable Fund, 1964-1978 (Box 27, Folder 375)
  - Hall, Anna C. - Estate of, 1968-1976 (Box 27, Folder 376)
  - Hall, Mrs. E. Snell, 1966-1975 (Box 27, Folder 377)
  - Hall, Frank B. Co., 1972-1978 (Box 27, Folder 377)
  - Hall, Frederick R., 1971-1979 (Box 27, Folder 378)
  - Halpin, Joseph, 1972-1976 (Box 27, Folder 379)
  - Hamilton College, 1964-1974 (Box 27, Folder 380)
  - Hamilton, Alan H., 1964-1974 (Box 27, Folder 380)
  - Hamilton, Clarence, 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 381)
  - Hamann, Mae J., 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 382)
  - Han, Ti-hou, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 382)
  - Hanley, Allen, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 382)
  - Harpster, Cyril B. - Trust, 1967-1979 (Box 27, Folder 383)
  - Harriff, Martha E., 1973-1979 (Box 27, Folder 384)
  - Hart, Donn V., 1968-1977 (Box 27, Folder 385)
  - Hartford Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 386)
  - Hartford Seminary Foundation, 1961-1975 (Box 28, Folder 387)
  - Hartzell-Norris Charitable Trust, 1967-1978 (Box 28, Folder 387)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute -Correspondence, 1971-1980 (Box 28, Folder 388-389)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute -Minutes, financial records, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 390)
  - Harvey, Pharis, 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 391)
  - Hatala, Robert, 1964-1973 (Box 28, Folder 392)
  - Hawaii, University of, 1962-1979 (Box 28, Folder 393)
  - Hawaii-Yenching Fund, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 393)
  - Hawaiian Trust Co., Ltd., 1971-1974 (Box 28, Folder 393)
  - Hawkins, Elza and Lois, 1975-1980 (Box 28, Folder 394)
  - Hawley, Mary B., 1968-1980 (Box 28, Folder 395)
  - Hay, Lawrence, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 396)
  - Hayes, E. Pearce, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 397)
  - Hayes, John D. and Barbara A., 1959-1963 (Box 28, Folder 398)
  - Hazen Foundation, 1975-1980 (Box 28, Folder 399)
  - Headley, Mrs. Leal, 1964-1981 (Box 29, Folder 400)
  - Heard, Mrs. Bartlett, 1963-1980 (Box 29, Folder 400)
  - Heebner, Flora K. - Memorial gift / Schwenkfelder Churches, 1965-1967 (Box 29, Folder 401)
  - Height, Dorothy, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 401)
  - Heimburger, Richard Ames, 1975-1978 (Box 29, Folder 402)
  - Heilman, Emily Muriel - Estate of, 1974-1978 (Box 29, Folder 403)
  - Herbert, Carol, 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 404)
  - Hess, Ceferino and David, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 405)
  - Hess, Edwin, 1976-1979 (Box 29, Folder 406)
  - Hill, Walker, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 407)
  - Hillman, Mrs. J. Hartwell, 1965-1979 (Box 29, Folder 407)
  - Hilscher, Harris G., 1972-1979 (Box 29, Folder 408)
  - Hiltner, Frederica M. - Estate of, 1970-1979 (Box 29, Folder 409)
  - Hinchcliff International, Inc., 1974-1978 (Box 29, Folder 410)
  - Hinkle, Emily, 1964-1979 (Box 29, Folder 410)
  - Hinkley, Leila M., 1976-1979 (Box 29, Folder 410)
  - Hinman, Kate Bailey - Estate of, 1964-1972 (Box 29, Folder 411)
  - Hirschberger, Lenice K., 1965-1976 (Box 29, Folder 412)
  - Hirst, Eric, 1961-1977 (Box 29, Folder 412)
  - Hirst, Mrs. J. W., 1964-1974 (Box 29, Folder 413)
  - Hobart, Kenneth G., 1962-1979 (Box 29, Folder 413)
  - Hodgson, Raymond, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 414)
  - Hoffsommer, Abigail, 1973-1979 (Box 29, Folder 415)
  - Hogue, Harland E., 1968-1979 (Box 29, Folder 416)
  - Holden, Reuben A., 1970-1979 (Box 29, Folder 417)
  - Holland, J. Gill, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 418)
  - Holland, Ira H., 1962-1968 (Box 29, Folder 419)
  - Holt, Jeannette R., 1962-1977 (Box 29, Folder 420)
  - Hon, Ping-kay, 1960-1964 (Box 29, Folder 420)
  - Hong Kong Christian Council, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 421)
  - Hoobler, Sibley W. and family, 1958-1979 (Box 30, Folder 422)
  - Hoover, Lyman, 1968-1982 (Box 30, Folder 423)
  - Horn, Francis Henry, 1965-1977 (Box 30, Folder 424,425)
  - Horton, Mildred, 1964-1978 (Box 30, Folder 426)
  - Horton, Walter M., 1959-1963 (Box 30, Folder 427)
  - Hotchkiss, Wesley A., 1971-1979 (Box 30, Folder 427)
  - Hovey, Rolf E., 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 428)
  - How, Bang - Estate of Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 429)
  - Howald, Reed, 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 430)
  - Howard, Ethel - Estate of, 1955-1972 (Box 30, Folder 431)
  - Howson, Gertrude and Hubert, 1962-1979 (Box 30, Folder 432)
  - Hsiao Ching-fen, 1977-1979 (Box 30, Folder 433)
  - Hsieh, Florence and Daniel, 1964-1979 (Box 30, Folder 434)
  - Hsieh, Pei-shih, 1962-1965 (Box 30, Folder 435)
  - Hsieh, Raymond Hsin Ching, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 436)
  - Hsieh, Wan-chen, 1970-1973 (Box 31, Folder 436)
  - Hsu, F. Richard, 1969-1979 (Box 31, Folder 437)
  - Hu, Ping-chuan, 1969-1976 (Box 31, Folder 438)
  - Hu, Shih-ying, 1973-1978 (Box 31, Folder 439)
  - Huang, Beulah, 1962-1966 (Box 31, Folder 439)
  - Huang, Esperanza, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 440)
  - Hubbard, Ruth, 1965-1982 (Box 31, Folder 440)
  - Huber, John, 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 441)
  - Huffman, Jean, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 442)
  - Humphrey, Roy and Joan, 1961-1971 (Box 31, Folder 443)
  - Hung, Frederick, 1961-1969 (Box 31, Folder 444)
  - Hungerford, Harlan and Irene, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 445)
  - Hunt, Chester L., 1961-1970 (Box 31, Folder 446)
  - Hunt, Frank R., 1960-1969 (Box 31, Folder 447)
  - Hunter, James A. and Maude, 1961-1968 (Box 31, Folder 448)
  - Hunter, Stanley A., 1971-1978 (Box 31, Folder 449)
  - Hutchins, Francis S., 1965-1975 (Box 31, Folder 449)
  - Hutchison, Ralph C., 1961-1966 (Box 31, Folder 450)
  - Hwang, Jae Y., 1971-1977 (Box 31, Folder 450)
  - Hylton, Paul, 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 451)
  - Hyun, Bong Hak, 1967-1979 (Box 31, Folder 452)
  - Ia - Ins (Box 31, Folder 453)
  - Int - Iz (Box 32, Folder 454-455)
  - Ihalauw, John, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 456)
  - Ihromi, Tapi Omas, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 457)
  - Illick, J. Theron and Bernice / Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1966-1978 (Box 32, Folder 458)
  - Illinois, State of - Religious Exemption, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 459)
  - Immanuel Congregational Church, Hartford CT, 1965-1978 (Box 32, Folder 460)
  - Imperial, George R., 1964-1979 (Box 32, Folder 461)
  - India: Ahmednagar College, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 462)
  - India: All-India Association for Christian Higher Education (AIACHE) -Correspondence: -Mani Jacob, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 463)
  - India: All-India Association for Christian Higher Education (AIACHE) -Correspondence: -T. A. Mathias, 1968-1978 (Box 32, Folder 464-466)
  - India: All-India Association for Christian Higher Education (AIACHE) -Correspondence: -Mathias / Thangaraj, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 467)
  - India: All-India Association for Christian Higher Education (AIACHE) -Proposal, grant, etc., 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 468)
  - India: American College, 1973-1979 (Box 33, Folder 469)
  - India: Colleges and universities - misc., 1962-1978 (Box 33, Folder 470)
  - India:Consultative Committee on Indian Colleges - Danforth Fdn., 1967-1974 (Box 33, Folder 471)
  - India: Ewing Christian College, 1968-1979 (Box 33, Folder 472,473)
  - India: Indian Christian Colleges: proposed survey, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 474)
  - India: ISS-FERES Project, 1964-1967 (Box 33, Folder 475)
  - India: Lucknow Christian College, 1968-1978 (Box 34, Folder 476)
  - India: Madras Christian College, 1962-1969 (Box 34, Folder 477)
  - India: Meston Training College, 1968-1980 (Box 34, Folder 478)
  - India: St. Christopher's Training College, 1970-1979 (Box 34, Folder 479)
  - India: St. John's College, 1973-1979 (Box 34, Folder 480)
  - India:Serampore College, 1964-1978 (Box 34, Folder 481)
  - India: Sophia College, 1973-1979 (Box 34, Folder 482)
  - India: Stella Maris College, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 483)
  - India: Student Christian Movement of India, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 484)
  - India:Taxation of charitable and religious trusts or institutions, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 485)
  - India: Isabella Thoburn College, 1970-1977 (Box 34, Folder 486)
  - India: United Theological College, Bangalore, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 487)
  - India: Vellore Christian Medical College and Hospital, 1974-1979 (Box 34, Folder 488)
  - India: Vellore Christian Medical College Board NYC, 1962-1979 (Box 34, Folder 489)
  - India: Women's Christian College, 1968-1974 (Box 34, Folder 490)
  - Indonesia: Association of Catholic Academic Institutions, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 491)
  - Indonesia: Atma Jaya Catholic University, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 492)
  - Indonesia: Christian University of Indonesia (Universitas Kristen Indonesia), 1964-1979 (Box 35, Folder 493-495)
  - Indonesia: Consulate General, 1962-1978 (Box 35, Folder 496)
  - Indonesia: Continental Commission for Church and Mission (KKKMI), 1963-1973 (Box 35, Folder 497)
  - Indonesia: Council of Churches: incl. Post Report, 1962-1975 (Box 35, Folder 498,499)
  - Indonesia: Ikip Sanata Dharma, 1975-1977 (Box 35, Folder 500)
  - Indonesia: Medical and health correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 501)
  - Indonesia: Methodist University of Indonesia, 1974-1979 (Box 35, Folder 502)
  - Indonesia: Misc. and background papers, 1971-1977 (Box 35, Folder 503)
  - Indonesia: Sekolah Tinggi Keguruan Dan Ilmu Pendidikan Kristen Makale (STKIP - Makale), 1975-1977 (Box 35, Folder 504)
  - Indonesia: Universitas Kristen Maranatha, 1970-1979 (Box 35, Folder 505)
  - Indonesia: Universitas Kristen Indonesia Paulus, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 506)
  - Indonesia: Universitas Nommensen, 1967-1976 (Box 35, Folder 506)
  - Institute of International Education, 1977-1979 (Box 36, Folder 507)
  - Institute of World Affairs / American Universities Field Staff, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 508)
  - Interchurch Center, 1972-1979 (Box 36, Folder 509-511)
  - International Christian Center for the Arts, Mexico, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 512)
  - International Christian Scholarship Foundation, 1969-1973 (Box 36, Folder 513)
  - International Council of Academic Institutions, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 514)
  - International Education Development Inc., 1968,1974 (Box 36, Folder 515)
  - International Foundation, 1971-1979 (Box 36, Folder 516)
  - Iowa, University of, 1972-1978 (Box 36, Folder 517)
  - Irving Trust Company, 1973-1979 (Box 36, Folder 518)
  - Irwin, Richard, 1962-1969 (Box 36, Folder 519)
  - Ja - Ji (Box 36, Folder 520)
  - Joa - Joh (Box 37, Folder 521-522)
  - Jacinto, Jose, 1962-1976 (Box 37, Folder 523)
  - Jackson, William R. and Lucille - Charitable Trust, 1965-1973 (Box 37, Folder 524)
  - Jacob, Korula, 1962-1967 (Box 37, Folder 525)
  - James, Arthur - Foundation, 1959-1964 (Box 37, Folder 526)
  - James, D. W. - Fund, 1958-1962 (Box 37, Folder 527)
  - James, Harry E., 1959-1968 (Box 37, Folder 527)
  - James, Walter C. - Foundation, 1967-1970 (Box 37, Folder 528)
  - Janda, Gretchen Ann, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 529)
  - Jani, A. C., 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 529)
  - Japan: General, A - Z (Box 37, Folder 530)
  - Japan: Council of Cooperation, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 531)
  - Japan: Doshisha University, 1965-1979 (Box 37, Folder 532)
  - Japan: Kwansei Gakuin, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 533)
  - Japan: Kwansei Gakuin / Satya Wacana Student Service Project, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 534)
  - Japan: Meiji Gakuin, 1968-1978 (Box 37, Folder 535)
  - Japan: Rikkyo University, 1962-1978 (Box 37, Folder 536)
  - Japan: Tohoku Gakuin University, 1976-1978 (Box 38, Folder 537)
  - Japan: Tokyo Women's Christian College, 1971-1978 (Box 38, Folder 538)
  - Jay, C. Douglas, 1971-1974 (Box 38, Folder 539)
  - Jenks, Jeffrey, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 539)
  - Jewett, George Frederick - Foundation, 1969-1979 (Box 38, Folder 540)
  - Joblin, Kingsley J., 1962 (Box 38, Folder 541)
  - Jockheck, Carl, 1971-1977 (Box 38, Folder 542)
  - Johannaber, John W., 1971-1976 (Box 38, Folder 543)
  - John, K. C., 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 544)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1969-1975 (Box 38, Folder 545)
  - Johns, Thomas, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 545)
  - Johnson, E. Ashby, 1967-1975 (Box 38, Folder 546)
  - Johnson Foundation / Wingspread Conference Center, 1965-1979 (Box 38, Folder 547)
  - Johnson, Robert G., 1971-1976 (Box 38, Folder 548)
  - Johnson, Roger A., 1967-1979 (Box 38, Folder 549)
  - Johnston Charitable Trust, 1962-1973 (Box 38, Folder 550)
  - Jones III, B. F., 1967-1979 (Box 38, Folder 551)
  - Jones, David, 1972-1975 (Box 38, Folder 551)
  - Jones, Donald Corwin, 1969-1972 (Box 38, Folder 552)
  - Jones, Edwin C. - Scholarship Fund, 1961-1974 (Box 38, Folder 553)
  - Jones, Francis Price and Emma Lucille, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 553)
  - Jones, Irene, 1971-1982 (Box 38, Folder 554)
  - Jones, J. Holton, 1965-1977 (Box 39, Folder 555)
  - Jones, Tracey K., 1965-1979 (Box 39, Folder 556)
  - Jones, W. Alton - Foundation, 1962-1976 (Box 39, Folder 556)
  - Joyce, Anette V. - Estate of, 1945-1966 (Box 39, Folder 557)
  - Judd, Walter, 1961-1979 (Box 39, Folder 558)
  - Junkin, William F., Jr. and III, 1959-1973 (Box 39, Folder 559)
  - Ka - Kim, A - K (Box 39, Folder 560-565)
  - Kim, L - Z - Kz (Box 40, Folder 566-569)
  - Kaisersatt, Lorraine A. - Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1974-1977 (Box 40, Folder 570)
  - Kalb, Melvyn, 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 571)
  - Kang, Kuo-wei, 1972-1974 (Box 40, Folder 572)
  - Kao, Frederick and Edith, 1965-1978 (Box 40, Folder 572)
  - Kao, John Yu-ling, 1963-1976 (Box 40, Folder 573)
  - Keane, Lucina, 1962-1979 (Box 40, Folder 574)
  - Keck, Wendell M., 1966-1979 (Box 40, Folder 574)
  - Kee, Norman Lau, 1962-1977 (Box 40, Folder 575)
  - Kehl, Francis S., 1962 (Box 40, Folder 575)
  - Keiran, Ethel L., 1975-1979 (Box 40, Folder 575)
  - Keiter, Herman and Dorothy, 1971-1974 (Box 40, Folder 576,577)
  - Keiter, Herman and Dorothy, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 578,579)
  - Keller, Wayne, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 580)
  - Kellogg, Flint, 1972-1979 (Box 41, Folder 581)
  - Kennard, Ralph B., 1972-1978 (Box 41, Folder 582)
  - Kennedy Institute of Ethics, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 583)
  - Kennedy, Carroll and Lois, 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 584)
  - Kennedy, Melville T., 1968-1979 (Box 41, Folder 584)
  - Kennelly, R. Grice, 1964-1975 (Box 41, Folder 585)
  - Kensington Congregational Church, CT, 1965-1978 (Box 41, Folder 585)
  - Kepler, A. R. - Memorial Scholarship, 1964-1971 (Box 41, Folder 586)
  - Kilborn, Leslie G., 1963-1968 (Box 41, Folder 587)
  - Kilborn, Janet McClure - Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1959-1965 (Box 41, Folder 588)
  - Kim, Byong Hack through Kim, Yong Joon (Box 41, Folder 589-595)
  - Kim, Yoon C., 1961-1975 (Box 42, Folder 596)
  - Kimura, Rihito, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 596)
  - King, Georgianna Brackett - Estate of, 1959-1969 (Box 42, Folder 597)
  - King, James Roy, 1963-1979 (Box 42, Folder 598)
  - Kirk, Florence, 1971-1979 (Box 42, Folder 599)
  - Kleinjans, Everett, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 600)
  - Ko, Siang Fo, 1955-1979 (Box 42, Folder 601)
  - Kohl, F. Marriott Small, 1968-1973 (Box 42, Folder 602)
  - Koinonia Foundation, 1965-1973 (Box 42, Folder 603)
  - Korea: -Asian University Chaplains' Workshop, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 604)
  - Korea: -Computer science consultant, 1971-1973 (Box 42, Folder 605)
  - Korea: -Fact sheets - re. human rights issues, 1974-1978 (Box 42, Folder 606)
  - Korea: -General (Box 42, Folder 607,608)
  - Korea: -Korea Emergency Faculty Support Fund, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 609)
  - Korea: -Korean ambassadors, 1969-1974 (Box 42, Folder 610)
  - Korea: -Korean Christian Scholars in N. America, Assn. of, 1971-1979 (Box 43, Folder 611,612)
  - Korea: -National Council of Churches in Korea, 1964-1978 (Box 43, Folder 613)
  - Korea: -NCCK NCCC/USA consultation, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 614)
  - Korea: -Seoul Woman's College, 1966-1979 (Box 43, Folder 615,616)
  - Korea: -Sogang University, 1970-1979 (Box 43, Folder 617,618)
  - Korea: -Soong-Sil College, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 619)
  - Korea: -Wilson, Stanton, 1967-1978 (Box 43, Folder 619)
  - Kownacki, Stanislaw, 1968-1972 (Box 43, Folder 620)
  - Kramer, Martha M, 1963-1979 (Box 43, Folder 621)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1958-1978 (Box 43, Folder 622,623)
  - Kress Foundation, 1964-1978 (Box 43, Folder 624)
  - Kriege, Owen H., 1959-1978 (Box 43, Folder 624)
  - Krug, Elsie Clark, 1964-1979 (Box 43, Folder 625)
  - Krull, Leonard M., 1958-1973 (Box 43, Folder 626)
  - Ku Min-chuan, 1964-1967 (Box 44, Folder 627)
  - Ku Tun-jou and I-ching, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 627)
  - Kuoksa, Gladys M., 1963 (Box 44, Folder 628)
  - Kwoh, Edwin and Beulah, 1967-1979 (Box 44, Folder 628)
  - Kwok, Gregory, 1957-1959 (Box 44, Folder 629)
  - Kwon, Kyong Nam, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 630)
  - Kwong, Siu Kong (Luke), 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 631)
  - Laa - Lim (Box 44, Folder 632-637)
  - Lin - Ly (Box 45, Folder 638-642)
  - Laale, Hans W., 1976-1979 (Box 45, Folder 643)
  - Lacy, Creighton B., 1964-1973 (Box 45, Folder 644)
  - Lacy, Henry A., 1968-1978 (Box 45, Folder 645)
  - Lai, Daniel, 1959-1977 (Box 45, Folder 646)
  - Lai, Wai-hang, 1963-1967 (Box 45, Folder 647)
  - Laird, Clinton M - Memorial Fund, 1959-1975 (Box 45, Folder 648)
  - Laird, Eleanor M. - Estate of, 1956-1957 (Box 45, Folder 649)
  - Lakewood Village Community Church, CA, 1964-1977 (Box 45, Folder 649)
  - Lam, Chee K., 1971 (Box 45, Folder 650)
  - Land, Roy, 1964-1965 (Box 46, Folder 651)
  - Landon, Kenneth P., 1967-1973 (Box 46, Folder 652)
  - Laney, James T., 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 652)
  - Langsjoen, Arne, 1968-1978 (Box 46, Folder 653)
  - Lapp, John A., 1977 (Box 46, Folder 654)
  - Lau, John, 1977-1979 (Box 46, Folder 655)
  - Lauby, Paul T., 1970-1979 (Box 46, Folder 656-660)
  - Lawson-Johnston, Peter, 1963-1974 (Box 46, Folder 661)
  - Leaman, Bertha R., 1958-1963 (Box 46, Folder 662)
  - Leavens, Dickson and Marjorie, 1964-1977 (Box 46, Folder 663)
  - Ledden, Henrietta Gibson and W. Earl, 1964-1977 (Box 46, Folder 664)
  - Lee, Beatrice, 1967-1969 (Box 46, Folder 665)
  - Lee, Peter and Shelley, 1968-1970 (Box 46, Folder 666)
  - Lee, P. William, 1971-1974 (Box 47, Folder 667)
  - Lee, Young Bin, 1972-1975 (Box 47, Folder 668)
  - Lefforge, Roxy, 1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 668)
  - Lehmann, Donald, 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 669)
  - Leiper, Henry Smith, 1965-1975 (Box 47, Folder 670)
  - Leisure World Community Church, CA, 1966-1979 (Box 47, Folder 671)
  - Lerrigo, Edith, 1974-1979 (Box 47, Folder 672)
  - Leung, S. C., 1964-1967 (Box 47, Folder 673)
  - Lewis, A. B., 1971-1979 (Box 47, Folder 674)
  - Lewis Clark College, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 675)
  - Lewis, Phillip, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 675)
  - Lewton, Joel C., 1974-1978 (Box 47, Folder 676)
  - Li Hung-chiang, 1964-1965 (Box 47, Folder 677)
  - Li - Lee wedding, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 678)
  - Liao Sheng-hsiung, 1972-1978 (Box 47, Folder 679)
  - Libraries - surveys, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 680)
  - Liem, Tjong Tiat, 1968-1970 (Box 47, Folder 681)
  - Lien, Donald S., 1964-1966 (Box 47, Folder 682)
  - Light, Timothy and Joy, 1965-1974 (Box 47, Folder 683)
  - Lilly, Ruth / Lilly Endowment, 1957-1966 (Box 47, Folder 684)
  - Lim, Chin-yeang, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 685)
  - Lim, Wan Ngo, 1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 685)
  - Lin, Chao-te, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 685)
  - Lin, Edgar, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 686)
  - Lin, Pi-yao, 1974-1976 (Box 47, Folder 687)
  - Lin, Sang-hsiung through Lin, Wen-chan (Box 48, Folder 688-691)
  - Lingnan College, Hong Kong, 1967-1979 (Box 48, Folder 692,693)
  - Lingnan University, Trustees of, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 694)
  - Lion's Club of Chinatown, NY, 1961-1968 (Box 48, Folder 695)
  - Liu, Chia-yu through Liu, Yu-chen (Box 48, Folder 696-701)
  - Lo, Mary, 1974-1976 (Box 48, Folder 702)
  - Lobenstine, Belle - Estate of, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 703)
  - Lockett, W. B., 1961-1978 (Box 48, Folder 704)
  - Lodwick, Robert C., 1970-1979 (Box 48, Folder 705)
  - Loeb, Rhoades, Hornblower Co., 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 706)
  - Loehr, George R., 1966-1976 (Box 48, Folder 706)